(Amy:)That was great. Rub my chest again.
(Sheldon:)No. I need to get you down for a nap.
(Sheldon:)And for some reason,
that VapoRub gets you all fired up.
- How's the poor thing?
- I'm hanging in there. Thanks for asking.
Hey, Amy, I brought you some drugs
we've been working on in the lab.
(Bernadette:)This is proving really good for congestion.
There's a chance
it can make tears burn like acid.
(Bernadette:)So if you take it, happy thoughts.
I'm gonna draw you a soothing bath.
(Sheldon:)- Where's your bath thermometer?
- I don't have a bath thermometer.
(Sheldon:)Fine, then I'm going to draw you...
(Sheldon:)...a nerve-wracking bath
of indeterminate temperature.
(Bernadette:)This is a really good expectorant.
(Bernadette:)Although, some test subjects reported lactating
uncontrollably when they heard music.
(Amy:)Okay, okay, here's the deal.
I don't need your medicine. I'm not sick.
- I don't understand.
- I got better two days ago.
(Amy:)It's just been so nice
having Sheldon take care of me.